A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1977-1981, RG 33 FA1503
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1977-1981; 33
  - Conservation, 1977-1981; 10
    - New York Zoological Society - Minutes-Meetings - Annual Members Meetings (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - New York Zoological Society - Minutes-Meetings - Board of Trustees (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - New York Zoological Society - Minutes-Meetings - Staff Meetings (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - New York Zoological Society - Minutes-Meetings - Executive Committee (Box 115, Folder 2-3)
    - New York Zoological Society - Printed Material (Box 116, Folder 1-2)
    - New York Zoological Society - Releases (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - New York Zoological Society - Reports (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - New York Zoological Society - Wild Asia (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Parks - A-Z (Box 116, Folder 6-7)
    - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - Board of Trustees (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - Contributions (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - Minutes-Meetings (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Parks - National Recreation and Park Association - Printed Material (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Parks - Parks Council (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Printed Material (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Resources for the Future (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Resources for the Future - Annual Reports (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S. (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - LSR-Conrad L. Wirth (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - Save the Redwoods League (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Scientists Institute for Public Information (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Scientists Institute for Public Information - Printed Matter (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Sierra Club Foundation (Box 118, Folder 3-4)
    - Sierra Club Foundation - Contributions (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Sierra Club Foundation - Frontera del Norte Fund (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Sierra Club Foundation - Printed Material (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital - Lyndon Baines Johnson Memorial Grove on the Potomac (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital - Lyndon Baines Johnson Memorial Grove on the Potomac - Booklet (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital - Lyndon Baines Johnson Memorial Grove on the Potomac - Finances (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital - Lyndon Baines Johnson Memorial Grove on the Potomac - Fund Raising (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital - Lyndon Baines Johnson Memorial Grove on the Potomac - Landscaping (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Society for a More Beautiful National Capital - Lyndon Baines Johnson Memorial Grove on the Potomac - Printed Material (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - Southwest Research and Information Center (Box 120, Folder 8)
    - Izaak Walton League of America (Box 120, Folder 9)
    - Water Pollution (Box 120, Folder 10)
    - Urban Environment Conference (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Wilderness Society (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - United States Government - A-Z (Box 121, Folder 3-4)
    - United States Government - Council on Environmental Quality (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - United States Government - Environmental Protection Agency (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - United States Government - National Commission on Water Quality (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - United States Government - Department of the Interior (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service A-Z (Box 122, Folder 4-5)
    - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - Printed Matter (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - Concessioners (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - Releases (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - National Park Foundation (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - National Park Foundation - A-Z (Box 123, Folder 4-5)
    - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - National Park Foundation - Annual Reports (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - National Park Foundation - Contributions (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - National Park Foundation - Minutes-Meetings (Box 124, Folder 2-3)
    - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - National Park Foundation - Printed Material (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - National Parks - A-M (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - National Parks - N-Z (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - National Parks - Acadia National Park (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - National Parks - Grand Teton National Park (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - National Parks - Grand Teton National Park - John D. Rockefeller Jr. Memorial Parkway (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - National Parks - Great Smoky Mountains National Park (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - National Parks - Haleakala National Park (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - National Parks - Haleakala National Park - Seven Sacred Pools (Box 126, Folder 1-2)
    - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - National Parks - Redwoods National Park (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - National Parks - Redwoods National Park - Clippings (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - National Parks - Virgin Island National Park (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - United States Government - Department of the Interior - National Park Service - National Parks - Wolf Trap Farm Park for the Performing Arts (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - United States Government - Presidents Environmental Quality Council - Citizens Advisory Committee on Environmental Quality (CACEQ) (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous States - A-E (Box 126, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous States - F-Z (Box 127, Folder 1-5)
    - Miscellaneous States - Hawaii (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous States - Maine (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous States - Maine - Natural Resources Council of Maine (Box 127, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous States - Alaska (Box 127, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous States - Massachusetts (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous States - Massachusetts - Massachusetts Audubon Society (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous States - Vermont (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - New York City - Central Park Conservancy (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - New York City - Department of Parks - A-Z (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - New York City - Department of Parks - NYC Parks, Recreational and Cultural Affairs Administration (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - New York City (Box 128, Folder 7)
    - New York City - Council of the Environment of NYC (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - New York City - Council on the Environment of NYC - Reports (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - New York State - A-M (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - New York State - N-Z (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - New York State - Adirondack Park Agency (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - New York State - Department of Environmental Conservation (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - New York State - Department of Environmental Conservation - Printed Matter (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - New York State - Hudson River Valley Commission (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - New York State - Michigan Hill (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - New York State - New York State Conservation Council (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - New York State - State Council of Parks - A-Z (Box 130, Folder 6-9)
    - New York State - State Council of Parks - Area Commission (Box 130, Folder 10)
    - New York State - State Council of Parks - Alleghany State Park Commission (Box 130, Folder 11)
    - New York State - State Council of Parks - Long Island State Park Commission - A-Z (Box 130, Folder 12)
    - New York State - State Council of Parks - New York City State Park Commission - Members (Box 130, Folder 13)
    - New York State - State Council of Parks - Area Commission - Palisades Interstate Park Commission (Box 130, Folder 14)
    - New York State - State Council of Parks - Area Commission - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - A-Z (Box 131, Folder 1-2)
    - New York State - State Council of Parks - Area Commission - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Annual Reports (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - New York State - State Council of Parks - Area Commission - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Budget-Meetings (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - New York State - State Council of Parks - Area Commission - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Clippings (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - New York State - State Council of Parks - Area Commission - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Commissioner Appointments (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - New York State - State Council of Parks - Area Commission - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Consolidated Edison (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - New York State - State Council of Parks - Area Commission - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Contributions (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - New York State - State Council of Parks - Area Commission - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Employees (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - New York State - State Council of Parks - Area Commission - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Employees - Nash Castro (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - New York State - State Council of Parks - Area Commission - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Lake Minnewaska State Park (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - New York State - State Council of Parks - Area Commission - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Memos (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - New York State - State Council of Parks - Area Commission - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Minutes-Meetings (Box 132, Folder 7-8)
    - New York State - State Council of Parks - Area Commission - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Printed Material (Box 132, Folder 9)
    - New York State - State Council of Parks - Area Commission - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - LSR (Box 132, Folder 10)
    - New York State - State Council of Parks - Area Commission - Palisades Interstate Park Commission - Releases (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - New York State - State Council of Parks - Budget-Finances (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - New York State - State Council of Parks - Commissioner Appointments (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - New York State - State Council of Parks - Minutes-Meetings (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - New York State - State Council of Parks - NYS - Board of Historic Preservation (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - New York State - State Council of Parks - Statewide Parks Advisory Committee (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - New York State - State Council of Parks - LSR (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - New York State - Department of Parks and Recreation Releases (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - New York State Historic Trust (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - Education - A-Z (Box 133, Folder 10)
    - Education - Shelburne Farms Resources, Inc. (Box 133, Folder 11, Box 134, Folder 1-3)
    - Foreign - A-B (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - Foreign - C-Z (Box 135, Folder 1-4)
    - Foreign - World Wildlife Fund (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - Foreign - World Wildlife Fund - Printed Material (Box 136, Folder 1-2)
    - Recreation - A-S (Box 136, Folder 3-5)
    - Recreation - T-Z (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Recreation - Caribbean Hotel Association (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Recreation - U.S. Ski Educational Foundation, Inc. (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - Recreation - Foreign (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - American Conservation Association (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - American Conservation Association - Contributions (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - D-E, 1977-1981; 11
    - D - Miscellaneous (Box 137, Folder 7-8)
    - Defense - Military Matters - A-Z (Box 138, Folder 1-2)
    - Defense - Veterans - A-Z (Box 138, Folder 3-4)
    - Defense - Veterans - National Association of Atomic Veterans (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Defense - Veterans - Navy League of the United States (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - Defense - Veterans - Philippine Veterans (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson - Takara Partners (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Dilworth, J. Richardson (Box 140, Folder 2-3, Box 141, Folder 1)
    - E - Miscellaneous (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Economics, 1977-1981; 12
    - Economics - A-B (Box 141, Folder 3-4)
    - Economics - B-C (Box 142, Folder 1-4)
    - Economics - D-K (Box 143, Folder 1-4)
    - Economics - L-R (Box 144, Folder 1-4)
    - Economics - S-Z (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Alliance for Free Enterprise (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - American Enterprise Institute for Public Policy Research (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - American Institute for Free Labor Development (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - American Woman's Economic Development Corporation (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Caribbean Council (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Center for Development Policy (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Center for Economic Organizing (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Center for Rural Affairs (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Council on Economic Priorities (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Council on Economic Priorities - Printed Matter (Box 147, Folder 2-3)
    - Don't Bankrupt Washington Legal Defense Fund (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Environmentalists For Full Employment (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Federation of Southern Cooperatives (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Grace, J. Peter (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - Illinois Public Council (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - Industrial States Policy Center (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - Jewish Labor Committee (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - Movement for Economic Justice (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - National Bureau of Economics Research (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - National Committee for Full Employment (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - Northeast-Midwest Institute (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - Northeast-Midwest Institute - Printed Matter (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - Operation Push (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - Printed Matter (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - Project Work (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - Trilateral Commission (Box 150, Folder 5, Box 151, Folder 1-3)
    - Trilateral Commission - Contributions (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - Trilateral Commission - Finances-Budget (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - Trilateral Commission - Minutes-Meetings (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - Trilateral Commission - A-Z, 1977-1981 (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - The Rockford Institute (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - The Rockford Institute - Printed Material (Box 152, Folder 4)
  - Education, 1977-1981; 13
    - Education - A-Cg (Box 153, Folder 1-4)
    - Education - Ch-F (Box 154, Folder 1-5)
    - Education - G-L (Box 155, Folder 1-6)
    - Education - M-N (Box 156, Folder 1-3)
    - Education - O-Z (Box 157, Folder 1-4)
    - Academy for Educational Development (Box 158, Folder 1)
    - American Philosophical Society (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies - Printed Matter (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies - Contributions (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - Association for Work and Learning (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - Center for the Analysis of Public Issues (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - Center for City Building Educational Programs (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - Center for the Study of Law and Politics (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - Center for Information on America (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Center for the Study of Responsive Law (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Earthwatch, 1977-1981 (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - Educational Testing Service (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - Institute for International Education Programs (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - Esalen Institute (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - Institute for Policy Studies, 1978-1981 (Box 161, Folder 2-3)
    - International Baccalaureate (Box 162, Folder 1)
    - International Federation of Institutes for Advanced Study (Box 162, Folder 2)
    - Lindisfarne Association, Inc. (Box 162, Folder 3-4)
    - The Martin Luther, King, Jr. Center for Social Change (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - A.J. Muste Memorial Institute (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - National Committee for Citizens in Education (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - National Geographic (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - National Geographic - Board of Trustees (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - National Geographic - Finances (Box 163, Folder 5, Box 164, Folder 1, Box 165)
    - National Geographic - Legal (Box 165, Folder 2)
    - National Geographic - Minutes-Meetings (Box 165, Folder 3-4)
    - National Geographic - Printed Material (Box 165, Folder 5)
    - National Geographic - Printed Material - Schedule of Articles (Box 165, Folder 6)
    - Nautilus International, Inc. (Box 166, Folder 1-2)
    - Sex Information and Education Council of the United States, Inc. (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - Woodlands Institute (Box 166, Folder 4)
    - Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institution (Box 167, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - A-Amg (Box 167, Folder 3-4)
    - Colleges - Amh-Ch (Box 168, Folder 1-4)
    - Colleges - Ch-E (Box 169, Folder 1-5)
    - Colleges - F-I (Box 170, Folder 1-3)
    - Colleges - J-M (Box 171, Folder 1-4)
    - Colleges - M-R (Box 172, Folder 1-4)
    - Colleges - S-University K (Box 173, Folder 1-4)
    - Colleges - University L-V (Box 174, Folder 1-3)
    - Colleges - W-Z (Box 175, Folder 1-2)
    - Colleges - Boston University (Box 175, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - Brown University (Box 175, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - City University of New York (Box 175, Folder 5)
    - Colleges - College of the Atlantic (Box 176, Folder 1-3, Box 177, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - College of the Atlantic - Contributions (Box 177, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - College of the Virgin Islands (Box 177, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - Columbia University (Box 177, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - Columbia University - Academy of Political Science (Box 177, Folder 5)
    - Colleges - Columbia University - Contributions (Box 178, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - Columbia University - Printed Material (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - Cornell University (Box 178, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - Cornell University - New York State College of Human Ecology (Box 178, Folder 4, Box 179, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - Cornell University - New York State College of Human Ecology - Printed Matter (Box 179, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - Cornell University - Printed Matter (Box 179, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - Dartmouth College - A-Z (Box 180, Folder 1-2)
    - Colleges - Dartmouth College - Alumni Fund (Box 180, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - Dartmouth College - Alumni (Box 180, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - Dartmouth College - Medical School (Box 181, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - Dartmouth College - Printed Material (Box 181, Folder 2-3)
    - Colleges - Emory University (Box 181, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - Georgetown University (Box 181, Folder 5)
    - Colleges - Georgetown University - Center for Strategic and International Studies (Box 181, Folder 6)
    - Colleges - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary (Box 182, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - Hampshire College (Box 182, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - A-G (Box 182, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - H-Z (Box 183, Folder 1-3)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Board of Overseers (Box 183, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Contributions - A-Z (Box 183, Folder 5)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - East Asian Studies (Box 184, Folder 1-3)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Fund Raising (Box 184, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Core Fund Drive (Box 184, Folder 5)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Core Fund Drive - DR Luncheon, 1978 March 9 (Box 185, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Core Fund Drive - DR Luncheon, 1978 February 10 (Box 185, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Core Fund Drive - DR Luncheon, 1977 November 28 (Box 185, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Graduate School of Business Administration (Box 185, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Graduate School of Business Administration - Fellowship for Women (Box 185, Folder 5)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Harvard College Fund (Box 185, Folder 6)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Harvard Divinity School (Box 186, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Harvard Divinity School - Printed Material (Box 186, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Harvard Divinity School - Rockefeller, John D. Jr. Memorial (Box 186, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Harvard Graduate Society for Advanced Study and Research (Box 186, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Harvard Law School (Box 186, Folder 5)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Harvard Medical School (Box 186, Folder 6)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Peabody Museum (Box 186, Folder 7)
    - Colleges - Harvard University - Printed Material (Box 187, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - Hobart and William Smith College (Box 187, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - Malboro Music (Box 187, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - Marymount College, Tarrytown (Box 187, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - A-R (Box 187, Folder 5-6)
    - Colleges - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - S-Z (Box 188, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Corporation Members (Box 188, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Minutes of Meetings (Box 188, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Printed Matter (Box 188, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Releases-Reports (Box 189, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Visiting Committees (Box 189, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - New School for Social Research (Box 189, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - New York Institute of Technology - New York College of Osteopathic Medicine - Fund Raising (Box 189, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - New York Institute of Technology - New York College of Osteopathic Medicine - Fund Raising - A-Z (Box 190, Folder 1-2)
    - Colleges - New York Institute of Technology - New York College of Osteopathic Medicine - Printed Matter (Box 190, Folder 3)
    - Colleges - New York Institute of Technology - New York College of Osteopathic Medicine (Box 190, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - New York Institute of Technology - New York College of Osteopathic Medicine - Nelson A. Rockefeller Academic Center (Box 191, Folder 1)
    - Colleges - New York University (NYU) (Box 191, Folder 2)
    - Colleges - Princeton University - A-Z (Box 192, Folder 1-3)
    - Colleges - Princeton University - Institute for Advanced Study (Box 192, Folder 4)
    - Colleges - Princeton University - Committee on Undergraduate Residential Life (Box 193, Folder 1)